Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2016 Acquisition, 1935-01-26-2003-12-05; 4.33; (4 boxes)
  - Burglar, circa 1986 (Box 177)
  - Bye Bye, Love, 1995-05-18 (Box 177)
  - Cancel My Reservation, 1971-07-12 (Box 177)
  - Celebration, 1960-12-15 (Box 177)
  - Celebration, 1961-01-17 (Box 177)
  - Colors, 1987-02-09 (Box 177)
  - Distant Thunder, 1987-02-20 (Box 177)
  - Dust, 1939-09-25 (Box 178)
  - Falling Stars: The Cavalcade of Hollywood, circa 1939 (Box 177)
    Released under the title "Hollywood Cavalcade."
  - Fresno, 1986; (4 folders) (Box 180)
    An archive for "Fresno," a television miniseries. Includes scripts for the series' 5 episodes, scene breakdowns, and storyboard sketches. Contains filmscript and a cutting of original binder.
  - Get Fisk, 1973-12-28 (Box 178)
  - The Glass Heart, circa 1945 (Box 177)
  - Highway Robbery, 1935-01-26 (Box 178)
  - The Human Comedy, 1942-08-28 (Box 178)
  - Interview with the Vampire, circa 1993 (Box 178)
  - Jason's Lyric, 1992-06-25 (Box 178)
  - The Last Picture Show, 1970-07-24 (Box 178)
  - Leroy Fisk, 1973-12-14 (Box 178)
  - Lethal Weapon, 1986-01-06 (Box 178)
  - Man of Mystery, 1944-06-07 (Box 178)
  - Matchstick Men, 2002-06-04 (Box 178)
  - Modern Romance, 1980-01-04 (Box 178)
  - My Blood Runs Cold, 1964-09-11 (Box 180)
  - Nob Hill, 1944-07-25 (Box 178)
  - Old Fish Hawk, circa 1979 (Box 178)
  - The Organization, 1971-03-22 (Box 178)
  - Out of the Past, 1983-03-10 (Box 178)
  - Play Misty for Me, 1970-09-08 (Box 179)
  - Poltergeist, 1981 (Box 179)
    Includes a first draftm and a collection of unbound pages from a variety of different revisions.
  - Psycho, 1960-05-06 (Box 180)
  - Psycho II, 1982-06-17 (Box 179)
  - The Revenge of Jupiter, 1983-07-29 (Box 179)
  - State Fair, 1961-09-14 (Box 179)
  - The Terminal Man, 1973-05-09 (Box 179)
  - The Thief Who Came to Dinner, 1972-02-07 (Box 179)
  - Thunder in God's Country, 1950-12-27 (Box 179)
  - Toys in the Attic, 1962-09-21 (Box 179)
  - The Travelers Part I, 1950-09-16 (Box 179)
    Released in 1951 under the title "Along the Great Divide."
  - Unlawful Entry, 1991-09-10 (Box 179)
  - Valley of the Dolls, 1967 (Box 179)
  - Viper Three, undated (Box 179)
  - W.C. Fields and Me, 1975-04-18 (Box 179)
  - Where Love Has Gone, 1963-10-10 (Box 179)
  - Wild Horses (Horseflesh), 1973 (Box 179)
    Includes a two page synopsis of the movie, with a brief note from talent agent Paul Kohner, referring the script to Charles Bronson.
- October 2016 Acquisitions, 1939-1990-02-10; 2.58; (3 boxes)
  - Bad Man of Deadwood, 1941-07-14 (Box 181)
    Script belonging to Hal Taliaferro, with his name on front wrapper and notations throughout. Alternate title "Outcasts of Poker Flats" written on front wraper.
  - The Clay Pidgeon, 1970-08-25 (Box 181)
  - Colorado, 1940-06-19 (Box 181)
    Contains script belonging to Hal Taliaferro.
  - The Court-Martial of George Armstrong Custer, 1977-06-20 (Box 181)
  - Deadeye, circa 1976 (Box 181)
    Contains a typed letter from producer Mike MacFarland to Martin Sheen's agent Maggie Abbott.
  - Deliver Us from Evil, circa 1970s (Box 181)
  - Down the Wyoming Trail, circa 1939 (Box 181)
    Contains shooting schedule sheets.
  - Incident in San Francisco, 1970-11-17 (Box 181)
  - Kachina, circa 1970s (Box 181)
  - Klondike, circa 1980s (Box 181)
  - Lacy and the Mississippi Queen, 1978-03-14 (Box 181)
  - L.A. Story, 1990-02-10 (Box 181)
  - Man Without a Gun, 1959-06-29 (Box 181)
    Contains television script for episode "Accused," a shooting schedule, a call sheet, and a photograph of actor Erik Cooper on the set.
  - Mohawk, circa 1956 (Box 181)
  - Oklahoma!, 1954-06-01 (Box 181)
  - Overland Trail Riders, 1952 (Box 181)
  - Prairie Chicken, 1942-05-29 (Box 181)
  - Riding Down Yesterday, circa 1970s (Box 181)
  - Rio Bravo, 1958-01-30 (Box 183)
  - Savage Seven, circa 1970s (Box 182)
  - South Pacific Trail, 1952 (Box 182)
    Script belonging to actor Rex Allen.
  - Sweet Surrender, circa 1980s (Box 182)
  - Tex, 1981-03-26 (Box 182)
- February 2017 Acquisition, 1971-08-20-1990-07-18; 1.08; (1 box)
  - Dead Heat, circa 1983 (Box 184)
    Released as "Courage" and as "Raw Courage."
  - Dragnet 1987, 1985-10-13 (Box 184)
  - The Last Run, 1985-06-06 (Box 184)
    Contains a memo from Burt Lancaster.
  - Main Event, 1978-09-12 (Box 184)
  - Middle Age Crazy, 1979-05-14 (Box 184)
  - Stand Up and Be Counted, 1971-08-20 (Box 184)
  - Terminator 2: Judgement Day, 1990-07-18; (2 folders) (Box 184)
    Contains: filmscript and original binder.